I'm from Norway. I have a marketing course for those who hate their jobs and want to
start their own business. I've been at a million for the last 10 years. I wanted to grow it the
last four years. I tell myself that Norway is the smallest market in the world, only 5 million people.
So that's what's stopping me. So the issue is that you feel like you're limited. I mean,
I don't think that Norway with 5 million residents is limiting to a million dollars a year. So I don't
think that's true. What are you doing to get customers? Right now we're just doing ads and
we do just two launches a year for the course. What stops you from doing it four times a year?
Just that launching is tiring. It's a bitch. Oh, it's a bitch. Got it. But the thing is,
you said, I want to grow my business. But you said, I was like, okay, let's just do more of
that thing that works. And you're like, but that's hard. It's not hard. It's just that it's just,
it's just me. So it's just me. Yeah, it's hard. I've been telling myself, so there's just 5 million
people. When you do ads in Norway, it's just the ad cost just explodes from 50 to 100.
Has anyone else seen that in the United States? It's not a Norway thing. It's a bad ads thing.
So the ways that you can solve this, you have a superior offer, conversion and optimization,
better ads. None of them are Norway. Okay. Do you make content?
Yes. How good is your content?
Mediocre. Okay. Thank you for being honest. If you get really good at content, ads are easy. And
so it might be actually a really good exercise for you to get better at your creative so that
when you run ads, you can actually know what makes a good ad, which is the same as what makes a good
creative. The only difference is that at the end you make a call to action, but I still prefer
do four times a year as the most obvious choice for doubling the business.